Telecommunications International Union Audio-Visual Materials 5758 AV
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Telecommunications International Union Audio-Visual Materials
1976-1983
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Telecommunications International Union
5758 AV
5.28 cubic feet
1 linear ft.
Audiovisual material.
Audio and some video recordings of the members of the Telecommunications International Union, including teleconferences, departmental conferences and meetings
9269743
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
M. Clark, January 11, 2016
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, April 02, 2019
Biographical / Historical
The majority of the members and officers of the Telecommunications International Union were women. At one time the union represented more than l00,000 telephone workers in the U.S. and Canada. At a special convention held in February l986 delegates voted to dissolve the TIU. Vice- President Joan Noonan remarked "we have earned a very distinguished place in the history of the labor movement... and we can hold our heads high and be proud."
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5758: Telecommunications International Union Records 5758 OH: Telecommunications International Union Oral History Interviews
Telecommunications International Union.
9269743
- TIU Teleconference - Reel 1, 1 (Box 1)
- TIU Teleconference - Reel 2, 2 (Box 1)
- AT&T Management Forum, James Olson, Chairman, AT&T Technologies: Part 1, 3 (Box 1)
- AT&T Management Forum, James Olson, Chairman, AT&T Technologies: Part 2, 4 (Box 1)
- I & M Realignment Explanation: 3/7/1983, 5 (Box 1)
- TIU button, 6 (Box 1)
- Departmental Conference 1982- Kevin Gnowe, May Kliesch (Box 2)
- Traffic Departmental Conference 1982 (Box 3)
- Departmental Conference - 1982 - Traffic (Box 4)
- Departmental Conference - 1982 - Traffic (Box 5)
- Departmental Conference - 1982 - Traffic (Box 6)
- Departmental Conference - 1982 - Traffic (Box 7)
- Plant Department Conference - #1 (Box 8)
- Plant Department Conference - #2 (Box 9)
- John (We Report); John + Bob (Organizing) - #2 (Box 10)
- 10/31 - Accounting (Box 11)
- Accounting - 3rd + 4th (Box 12)
- Traffic Departmental Conference - (5) (Box 13)
- Apr. Services Break Out (side III, side IV) (Box 14)
- Tanning (3, 4) (Box 15)
- Glen + John (Box 16)
- 1/10/1979 (Box 17)
- 1/11/1979 (Box 18)
- Accounting - 1st side - 1:45 pm; 2nd side - 2:15 pm: 10/30/1979 (Box 19)
- Bob (Box 20)
- Accounting Mtg. - 4/23/1980 (Box 21)
- Traffic - tape 6 (Box 22)
- Thursday - John on National Bargaining - tape #1(side 1); Matthew Aeena B.N.A., Frank Garon - side 2 (Box 23)
- Traffic - tape #5 (Box 24)
- Departmental Conference (1) [tape #1, side A]; Departmental Conference (2) [tape #1, side B] (Box 25)
- tape #3 (Box 26)
- TIU Accounting Department #5 + #6 11/15/1976 (Box 27)
- Tape #2 - A (Box 28)
- B. Leventhal, B. Grisly, Att: A. Weiner (side 1); Weiner Cont., Keven Growe (side 2) (Box 29)
- John Closing remarks (Box 30)
- Traffic Departmental Conference - side 1: Nat'l. Trends-bargaining, Resolutions; side 2 -- Closing remarks (Box 31)
- Traffic - tape #4 (side 1) (Box 32)
- Don Ephlin, Kay Dressler (Box 33)
- 1st - 10/31 - Summary Meeting (Box 34)
- Accounting - tape 1, side 1: 4/23/1980 (Box 35)
- Abe - Start of Don Ephlin (Box 36)
- Accounting (Box 37)
- Traffic Breakout #1 (Box 38)
- Unlabeled (Box 39)
- Unlabeled (Box 40)
- Unlabeled (Box 41)
- Unlabeled (Box 42)
- Unlabeled (Box 43)
- Unlabeled (Box 44)